

CONTACT



Address

16 Duiker Road,...Cape Town, 7769



Email

kanyisomadlebe@yahoo.com



Phone 064-747-3024

EXPERTISE SKILLS

- Data Science Foundation
- Big Data Foundation
- Beyond the Basics: Istio and IBM CKS

EXPERIENCE

UVUAFRIKA Learnership | 2023 - 2023

UVUAFRIKA Internship | 2023 - Current

KANYISO MADLEBE

Information Technology

ABOUT ME

ICT professional specializing in Business Analysis. Skilled in analyzing complex systems, identifying requirements, and implementing practical solutions. Effective communicator and collaborator with a track record of delivering projects on time. Dedicated to staying current with the latest ICT trends and technologies to drive organizational success.

EDUCATION

Information Technology

Walter Sisulu University | 2020 - 2022

 Diploma in ICT in Business Analysis.

Matric

Khanyisa High School | 2019

• Grade 12.

REFERENCE

Mr R.Ngandu HOD at WSU-IT|047 4016232

Thandi Ndaba Candidate Manager| 084 806 3374

Mrs NP.Madlebe Mother | 0733 348 4983